emedco.com 2006-06-26

# emedco Privacy Statement

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy has been amended as of July 24, 2001 to provide you with more detail regarding how we use the information that you supply us.

Emedco is committed to protecting your privacy. We have made new commitments to you - it's a part of our approach to keep evolving to provide you better service, while working to meet your expectations. The information that is collected is used to ensure secure ordering and provide a personalized shopping experience. See below for detailed information on what information we collect and how it is used.  
  
**Information Collection and Use**  
Emedco is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Emedco collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  
   
**What information do we collect from you?**  
**Registration**  
In order to access certain section of emedco.com, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.  
   
**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. Users who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive a telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they placed on-line. We will not share your phone number with other organizations.  
   
**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site, but they will not be able to use the shopping cart nor order products. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  
   
**Log Files**  
For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and IP address (where possible), but not the e-mail address. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Domain names and IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
   
**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we emedco are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
   
**Mail Preference**  
We occasionally make our valued customer names available to carefully screened companies offering goods & services through the mail that we think may be of interest to you. If you choose not to receive such offers, please [CONTACT US](mailto:mailing_list@emedco.com) and allow 90 days to take effect.   
   
**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.  
   
**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  
   
**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed.  
   
**How do we protect the security of your information?**  
**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [customerservice@emedco.com](mailto:customerservice@emedco.com).  
  
**Email Verification**  
We send all new customers a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out information below.  
   
**How do I opt-out of emedco's direct marketing programs?**  
**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our registration form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who want to purchase product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing us at [unsubscribe@emedco.com](mailto:unsubscribe@emedco.com) or by writing to us at the address listed below and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending [email](mailto:mailing_list@emedco.com) to us or by writing to us at the above address. Please let us know if you do not wish to receive information on new emedco products and services or if you simply want your name removed from the list we share with other organizations.  
  
**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send users, site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.  
   
**Notification of Changes**  
If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
   
**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send users, site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.  
   
**Changes to this Policy**  
We reserve the right to change this Policy from time to time and in our sole discretion. If the Policy for this Site changes, the revised policy will be posted at the "Privacy Policy" link on this Site's home page. Please check the Policy frequently and particularly before you submit additional information via the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes acceptance of such changes in the Policy. This Privacy Policy was last revised November, 2005.  
   
**Trademarks**  
The trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") displayed on this site are registered and unregistered Trademarks of Emedco in the United States and other countries (trademark denotations on the Emedco websites indicate federal registrations in the United States). Nothing contained on the Brady Corporation website should be construed as granting by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on the Emedco websites without the written permission of Emedco or such third party that may own the Trademark. Misuse of any Trademarks, or any other content, displayed on the Emedco websites is prohibited. Emedco aggressively enforces its intellectual property rights, including via civil and criminal proceedings.  
   
**How do I update my account information?**  
**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. You can update your information at the member information page or by [emailing](mailto:customerservice@emedco.com) our Customer Support.  
   
**Our postal address is:**  
P.O. Box 369  
Buffalo, New York 14240-0369  
We can be reached via e-mail at [customerservice@emedco.com](mailto:customerservice@emedco.com),   
or you can reach us by telephone at 716-626-1616.
